UA Presents Records 1991 - 2011
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
UA Presents Records 1991 - 2011
MS 566
UA Presents
The UA Presents Records contains materials related to the performing arts series seasons at the University of Arizona, spanning the years of 1991 to 2011.
10 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/ E-Mail: LBRY-askspcoll@email.arizona.edu
Restrictions
There are no restrictions on this collection.
Biographical Note
Originally known as the Office of Cultural Affairs until 1995, UA Presents is the official performing arts presenter of the University of Arizona, that brings art and cultural events to Centennial Hall on campus. Throughout its existence, the series put on has included performances in theatre, dance, spoken word, classical, jazz and world music.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into 3 series
Series I: UA Presents Series Seasons Materials, 1995 - 2011
Series II:UA Presents Organization Materials, 1991 - 2009
Series III: Miscellaneous Artist and Theater Materials, 2000 - 2002
Scope and Content Note
The collection contains materials including programs, marketing information, flyers, and published articles on the organization itself, on its former director Ken Foster, on the series of events UA Presents has put on, as well as various artist and theater marketing materials.
Access Terms
Foster, Ken.
University of Arizona.
Performing Arts.
Theater.
Musicals.
Plays.
Tucson – Arizona.
Container List
- UA Presents Series Seasons Materials, 1995 - 2011; Series I
  Arranged chronologically, this series contains the programs, marketing materials, flyers, and published articles on UA Present's shows of past seasons from 1995 – 2011.
  - Angels in America, September 2, 1995 – September 24, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ballet Folkorico Nacional de Chile, October 10, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Wynton Marsalis and the Lincoln Center Jazz Orchestra, September 30, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Paco de Lucia, October 19, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cats, October 20, 1995 – October 22, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Penn and Teller, October 24, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Chamber Orchestra Kremlin, October 25, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - BB King, October 31, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Andreas Vollenweider and Friends, November 1, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dance Theatre of Harlem, November 4, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Kroumata, November 8, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Manhattan Transfer, November 13, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Mozarteum Orchestra of Salzbury, November 14, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Paul Winter's Solstice Journey, November 26, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Klezmar Conservatory Band, January 18, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Eiko and Koma in Wind, January 26, 1996 – January 27, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Lines Contemporary Ballet, January 31, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Broadway Swings, February 9, 1996 – February 11, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - STOMP, February 13, 1996 – February 14, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Compaynie Marie Chouinard, February 23, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Slide Hampton and the Jazz Masters, February 25, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Urban Bush Women, March, 2, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Dancers and Musicians of Bali, March 7, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Marion McPartland's Piano Jazz, March 9, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Los Folkoristas, March 22, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - St. Louis Symphony Orchestra, March 25, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - New York City Opera National Company "La Traviata", April 13, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Contraband, April 27, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Dance Brazil, May 4, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Ain't Misbehaving, May 10, 1996 – May 12, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Harry Belafonte, September 16, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Twyla Tharp/Tharp Dance, October 2, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Olodum, October 2, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Voices of Light, October 7, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Ballet Folkorico Quetzalli de Veracruz, October 26, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - St. Paul Chamber Orchestra, October 30, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - The Who's Tommy, November 1, 1996 – November 13, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - The Guitar Power Trio, November 7, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Tibetan Song and Dance Ensemble, November 9, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - David Rousseve/Reality, November 21, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Steve Reich and Musicians, November 22, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Canadian Brass Holiday Celebration, November 30, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Sweet Honey in the Rock, December 11, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Fiesta Navidad, December 14, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Lorie Line and Her Pop Chamber Orchestra, December 20, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Verve Jazz Fest, January 11, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Warsaw Philharmonic Orchestra, January 21, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Sacred Music, Sacred Dance, January 24, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Sukay, January 25, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - STOMP, January 28, 1997 – January 29, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Liz Lerman Dance Exchange, February, 1, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Samulnori, February 7, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - The Gospel at Columbus, February 14, 1997 – February 16, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Drums Across Cultures, February 20, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Kronos Quartet, February 22, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - The Joshua Redman Band, February 28, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Peking Acrobats, March, 12, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Alvin Ailey American Dance Theatre, March 6, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Yo-Yo Ma, March, 13, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Elizabeth Streb, March 26, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - David Dorfman Dance, April 5, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - String Trio of New York and the Bang on a Can All Star, April 9, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Kiss of the Spider Woman, April 11, 1997 – April 13, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - New York City Opera National Company - La Boheme, April 18, 1997 – April 19, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Ballet Hispanico of New York, April 26, 1997 – April 27, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - National Symphony Orchestra, May, 9, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Herbie Hancock and Wayne Shorter, September 26, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Ondekoza, September 30, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Tallin Chamber Orchestra, October 3, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Tango x2, October 11, 1997 – October 12, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Inti-Illimani, October 17, 1997 – October 18, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Philip Glass, October 21, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - House of Blues, October 22, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Deutsches Symphony, November 7, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - John McLaughlin, November 8, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Ani DiFranco, November 11, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Ballet Arizona, November 14, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - STOMP, December 2, 1997 – December 3, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Christmas Carol, December 7, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Fiesta Navidad, December 14, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - NYC Opera, January 21, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Tim Miller, January 24, 1998 – January 31, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Pilobolus, February 6, 1998 – February 7, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Coyote Consort, February 7, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Viva Arizona, February 18, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Andre Watts, February 20, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Peking Opera, February 27, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Stuart Pimsler Dance and Theatre, March 7, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Global Divas, March 12, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Cleo Laine, March, 13, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Peter, Paul, and Mary, March 21, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Mingus, March 27, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Amy Grant, March 29, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Spalding Gray, April 2, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Los Munequitos de Matanzas, April 5, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Bill T Jones, April 18, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Israel Camerata, April 19, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Bonnie Raitt, April 21, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Paco Pena, April 23, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Queen Ida and the Con Temps Zydeco Band, April 25, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Marsalis/Stravinsky, May 1, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Houston Ballet, May 7, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Suzy Bogguss, May 9, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - State Fair, May 13, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Mark O'Connor, May 19, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Le Ballet National du Senegal, October 1, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - The Repugnant Story of Clotario Demoniax, October 2, 1998 – October 3, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Short Stories, October 3, 1998 – October 4, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Mark Morris Dance Group, October 6, 1998 – October 7, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - James Galway, October 9, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Anonymous 4, October 18, 1998 – October 19, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - The Whirling Dervishes, October 21, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - The King and I, October 23, 1998 – October 24, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Trio Voronezh, October 29, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Penn and Teller, November 4, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Marisa Monte, November 13, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Ballet Arizona, November 7, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Rent, November 17, 1998 - November 22, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Damn Yankees, November 21, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Fiesta Navidad, December 12, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - San Jose Taiko, January 22, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Asian American Jazz Orchestra with San Jose Taiko, January 23, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Denyce Graves, January 27, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Kronos Quartet, January 28, 1999 – January 30, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Ballet Nacional de Cuba, February 3, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Meryl Tankard Australian Dance Theatre, February 9, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Orpheus Chamber Orchestra, February 12, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fiddler on the Roof, February 13, 1999 – February 14, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Coyote Consort, February 23, 1999 – February 25, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Rachel Rosenthal Company, February 24, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Philadanco, February 27, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Faddis, Hampton, and Heath, March 5, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Les Miserables, March 9, 1999 – March 14, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Lincoln Center Jazz Orchestra, March 23, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Monsters of Grace, March 25, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - The Flying Karamazov Brothers, April 2, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - The Margaret Jenkins Dance Company, April 10, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Mandy Patinkin, April 6, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Orquesta Sinfonica Nacional de Mexico, April 15, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cirque Ingenieux, April 17, 1999 – April 18, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - The Chieftains, April 28, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The Parsons Dance Company, April 30, 1999 – May 1, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Noise/Funk, May 4, 1999 – May 9, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Bobby McFerrin, September 17, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - BIG, September 26, 1999 – September 27, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Itzhak Perlman, September 29, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Sankai Juku, October 9, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Chicago, October 13, 1999 – October 17, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Tap Dogs, October 22, 1999 – October 23, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Virginia Rodrigues, October 26, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Mary Black, October 30, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Buena Vista Social Club, November 21, 1999 – November 22, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Paco De Lucia and Septet, November 4, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Emerson String Quartet, November 6, 1999 – November 7, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Eliot Risk and Burhan Ocal, November 9, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - The Carnegie Hall Jazz Band, November 12, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - David Rousseve/Reality, November 19, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - MTV's Campus Invasion Tour, November 20, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Riverdance, November 30, 1999 – December 5, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Lily Tomlin, December 11, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Royal Philharmonic Orchestra, January 18, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Ballet Hispanico, January 21, 2000 – January 23, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Coyote Consort - Young Beethoven, January 28, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Chanticleer, February 4, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - The Hallelujah Project, February 9, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Miss Saigon, February 10, 2000 – February 20, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - The Petersen Quartet, February 11, 2000 – February 12, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Magic Frequencies, February 23, 2000 – February 27, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Hallelujah!, March 4, 2000 – March 5, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - The Liz Lerman Dance Exchange, March 4, 2000 – March 5, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Joyful Noise, March 16, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - The English Concert, March 18, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Voices from the Margin, March 23, 2000 – March 26, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Newport Jazz, March 30, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Children of Uganda, April 4, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Alvin Ailey, April 8, 2000 – April 9, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - The Mandinka Epic, April 14, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Colorado String Quartet, April 15, 2000 – April 16, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Show Boat, April 18, 2000 – April 23, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Eric Idle, April 30, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - The Kirov Orchestra, September 12, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Cabaret, September 19, 2000 – September 24, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Buena Vista Social Club, September 25, 2000 – September 26, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Martha Graham Dance Company, September 30, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Nicholas Payton, October 7, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Yo-Yo Ma, October 12, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Brazil Night, October 14, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Ratan Thiyam, October 17, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Dracula/Philip Glass, October 20, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - BB King, October 23, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - STOMP, October 27, 2000 – October 29, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Nadja Salerno Sonnenberg, November 2, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Kate Clinton, November 3, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Ravi Shankar and Anoushka Shankar, November 4, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Academy of Ancient Music, November 9, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Voices of Mali, November 11, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Remember Shakti, November 15, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Bale Folklorico da Bahia, November 16, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Marcus Roberts Trio, November 18, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - The Immigrant Experience, November 27, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Ragtime, November 28, 2000 – December 3, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - The Boys Choir of Harlem, December 9, 2000 – December 10, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - AIDA, January 8, 2001 – January 13, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Coyote Consort, January 13, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Tucson Arts Odyssey, January 14, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Rent, January 16, 2001 – January 21, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Pilobolus, January 26, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - The Boston Camerata, January 26, 2001 – January 27, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Aeros, February 2, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Spirituals to Swing, February 3, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Jubilant Sykes, February 6, 2001 – February 9, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Riverdance, February 6, 2001 – February 11, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Cultures in Context – Hawai'i, February 11, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Halau Hula Ka No’eau, February 13, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Moscow Festival Ballet, February 15, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Spalding Gray, February 16, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - David Dorfman Dance, February 24, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Carnaval Veracruzano, February 27, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Anonymous 4, March 1, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Cultures in Context – Russia, March 4, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Bang on a Can All-Stars, March 6, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Chorovaya Akademia, March 10, 2001 – March 11, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - The Academy of St. Martin in the Fields, March 17, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Unlocking the Creative Process, March 22, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Lisa Kron – “2.5 Minute Ride”, March 23, 2001 – March 24, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Fosse, March 27, 2001 – April 1, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - The King’s Stag, April 6, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Regina Carter Quintet, April 7, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, April 14, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Eric Bogosian, April 20, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Urban Bush Women, April 28, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Los Lobos, August 26, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Dance, The Spirit of Cambodia, September 15, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Ali Akbar Khan, September 21, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - A Vision of Women, September 30, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Lincoln Center Jazz Orchestra, September 30, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Houston Ballet, October 3, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bayanihan, October 5, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Cesaria Evora, October 9, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Hancock, Brecker, and Hargrove, October 13, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Yamato, October 18, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Gewandhaus Orchestra of Leidzig, October 19, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Youssou N'Dour, October 20, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Ballet Nacional de Cuba, October 23, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Cookin', October 26, 2001 – October 28, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Stimmen World Voices Festival, November 2, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Noa, November 4, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Rodrigues, November 6, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Bangarra Dance Theatre, November 8, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Emanuel Ax and Yefim Bronfman, November 9, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - David Russell, November 14, 2001 – November 16, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Swing!, November 20, 2001 – November 25, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Los Fakires, November 30, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - The Vagina Monologues, December 2, 2001 – December 14, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Cirque, December 4, 2001 – December 9, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Streb, January 19, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Juilliard String Quartet, January 19, 2002 – January 20, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Contact, January 22, 2002 – January 26, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Buena Vista Social Club, January 23, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Rennie Harris Puremovement, January 26, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - National Acrobats of Taiwan, January 30, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Unlocking the Creative Process, January 2002 - February 2002 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - David Daniels, February 6, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Tim Miller – Glory Box, February 7, 2002 – February 8, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Ronald K. Brown/Evidence, February 9, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Banned in the USA, February 10, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Grigorovich Ballet, February 14, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Jerry Seinfeld Live, February 14, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Tim Miller - Glory Box, February 15, 2002 – February 16, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Turtle Island String Quartet, February 19, 2002 – February 20, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Estonian Philharmonic Chamber Choir, February 21, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Albita, February 23, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Alvin Ailey Dance Theater, March 1, 2002 – March 3, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Newport Jazz 2002, March 6, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Antonio Marquez, March 8, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Renee Fleming, March 14, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Ballet Hispanico, March 23, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Nrityagram, March 30, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Charlie Victor Romeo, April 9, 2002 – April 21, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - The Phantom of the Opera (1 of 2), April 10, 2002 – May 4, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - The Phantom of the Opera (2 of 2), April 10, 2002 – May 4, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Santiago Jimenez, Jr., August 25, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - 7th Congressional District Candidates, September 4, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Lila Downs, September 5, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Jaime Camil, September 21, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Ballet Folklorico de Mexico, September 26, 2002 – September 27, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Emerson String Quartet, October 1, 2002 – October 2, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Mickey Hart and Bembe Orisha, October 2, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Mandy Patinkin, October 8, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bill T. Jones, October 10, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Le Ballet National du Senegal, October 15, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - John Williams and Friends, October 16, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Sankai Juku, October 19, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Arizona Opera Company "La Traviata", October 19, 2002 – October 20, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - La Pasion Segun San Marcos, October 22, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Dianne Reeves, October 24, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Orquesta Sinfonico Nactional de Mexico, October 26, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Brazil, October 27, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Boston Camerata, November 1, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Caetano Veloso, November 2, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Kronos Quartet, November 7, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - The Shanghai Ballet, November 9, 2002 – November 10, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Blast, November 12, 2002 – November 17, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Ballet Preljocaj, November 14, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Yin Mei Dance, November 15, 2002 – November 16, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Masterpieces of the Russian Underground, November 6, 2002 – November 18, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Mark Morris Dance Group, November 23, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Neil Goldberg's Cirque, December 3, 2002 – December 8, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - TcheTche, December 12, 2002 – December 13, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - The Full Monty, December 17, 2002 – December 22, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - The Chieftains, January 14, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Poncho Sanchez, January 30, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Eiko and Koma, January 31, 2003 – February 1, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Prokofiev, February 5, 2003 – February 9, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Royal Winnipeg Ballet, February 8, 2003 – February 9, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Kodo, February 15, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Cleo Parker Robinson Dance, February 22, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Les Miserables, February 26, 2003 – March 2, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Limon Dance Company, March 2, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Tabla Beat Science, March 7, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Kathy Mattea, March 8, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Barrage, March 14, 2003 – March 16, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Peking Opera of Jilin, March 19, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Kenny Barron's Canta Brasil, March 22, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Urban Bush Women, March 27, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Nexus, March 29, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - The Stuttgart Ballet, April 1, 2003 – April 2, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Buena Vista Social Club, April 6, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - The Academy of Ancient Music, April 10, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance, April 12, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Spalding Gray, April 23, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Mamma Mia, April 30, 2003 – May 11, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Eugenia Leon, September 13, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Branford Marsalis, September 19, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - African Arts Festival, September 20, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - U Theatre of Taiwan, September 30, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Akram Khan, October 4, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Rennie Harris Puremovement, October 4, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - St. Lawrence String Quartet, October 15, 2003 – October 16, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 8)